const quizDataSintonim = [
    {
        question: '1. Konveks >< ...',
        options: ['Nyata', 'Cekung', 'Bias', 'Cembung'],
        answer: 'Cekung',
    },
    {
        question: '2. Kekang >< ...',
        options: ['Hewan', 'Bebas', 'Batas', 'Kebas'],
        answer: 'Bebas',
    },

    {
        question: '3. Sekuler >< ...',
        options: ['Tradisional', 'Keagamaan', 'Duniawi', 'Keberagaman'],
        answer: 'Keagamaan',
    },

    {
        question: '4. Makar >< ...',
        options: ['Baik', 'Pakar', 'Mekar', ' Sentosa'],
        answer: 'Baik',
    },

    {
        question: '5. Gegai >< ...',
        options: ['Lemah', 'Bohong', 'Geger', 'Kuat'],
        answer: 'Kuat',
    },

    {
        question: '6. Mortalitas = ......',
        options: ['Angka kelahiran', 'Angka kematian', 'Angka Kesehatan', 'Angka Kuadrat'],
        answer: 'Angka kematian',
    },

    {
        question: '7. Nuansa = ......',
        options: ['Perbedaan unsur makna', 'Perbedaan Pandangan', 'Irama', 'Perbedaan berat'],
        answer: 'Perbedaan unsur makna',
    },

    {
        question: '8. Proteksi = ......',
        options: ['Pengamanan', 'Pengawalan', 'Perlindungan', 'Penjagaan'],
        answer: 'Perlindungan',
    },

    {
        question: '9. Strata = ......',
        options: ['Setara', 'Kuliah', 'Halus', 'Tingkatan'],
        answer: 'Tingkatan',
    },

    {
        question: '10. Tendensi = ......',
        options: ['Kecenderungan', 'Ruangan', 'Denyut Nadi', 'Lawan'],
        answer: 'Kecenderungan',
    },
];